autojunction.co.za 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

  1. Introduction
  2. Information Collection & Use
  3. CareerSeeker Registration
  4. Recruiter Registration
  5. Auto Dealer Registration
  6. Property Agent Registration
  7. Resume
  8. Profile 
  9. Cookies
  10. Log Files
  11. Sharing
  12. Links
  13. Communications
  14. Security and Data Storage
  15. Choice/Opt Out
  16. Blog Disclosure
  17. Notification Of Changes
  18. Contact Us

**1\. Introduction** ****

[www.junction.co.za](http://www.junction.co.za/) is a Social business network built around professional and user generated career, auto and property content. This includes articles, ideas, questions, answers, links and comments. Users are able to customise content by topic and location, watch specific content, follow specific authors, comment on posts and create their own posts. The purpose of Junction is to create a discussion forum around career, auto and property.

[www.autojunction.co.za](http://www.autojunction.co.za/) is an online auto advertising and lead generation solution that works as an intermediary between Seekers, Dealers, Buyers and Sellers of vehicles.

[www.propertyjunction.co.za](http://www.propertyjunction.co.za/) is an online property advertising and lead generation solution that works as an intermediary between Seekers, Agents, Buyers, Developers and Sellers of properties.

AutoJunction and PropertyJunction are divisions of the PA Junction and form part of the legal entity PA Junction (Pty) Ltd which in turn is a subsidiary of the legal entity Interactive Junction Holdings (Pty) Ltd. Junction is a division and forms part of the legal entity Interactive Junction Holdings (Pty) Ltd. All terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy are applicable to all divisions and subsidiaries of Interactive Junction Holdings (Pty) Ltd.

The Company s referred to herein as "CareerJunction" refers to Interactive Junction Holdings and any of its divisions, including but not limited to:

**2\. Information Collection & Use** ****

CareerJunction is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. CareerJunction collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

**3\. CareerSeeker Registration** ****

In order to use the functionality of this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give the following information:

  * Full Name
  * Phone Number
  * Email Address
  * City or Town & Country (Province)
  * Username
  * Password
  * Communications(Yes/No)

This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest.

**4\. Recruiter Registration** ****

Information that is collected from subscribing Recruiters will be used to contact the Recruiter about the services for which they have expressed interest. If Recruiters want to change their information their company supervisor has access to do this using the Supervisor Tools functionality.

  * Company Name
  * Phone Number
  * Facsimile Number
  * Email Address
  * Website Address
  * City or Town & Country (Province)
  * Communications(Yes/No)

**5\. Auto Dealer Registration**

Information that is collected from subscribing dealers will be used to contact the dealer about the services for which they have expressed interest. If dealers want to change any of their details listed below they can contact our Client Services Department on [info@autojunction.co.za](mailto:info@autojunction.co.za).

  * Company Name
  * Phone Number
  * Facsimile Number
  * Email Address
  * Website Address
  * City or Town & Country (Province)
  * Communications(Yes/No)

**6\. Property Agent Registration**

Information that is collected from subscribing agents will be used to contact the agents about the services for which they have expressed interest. If agents want to change any of their details listed below they can contact our Client Services Department on [info@propertyjunction.co.za](mailto:info@propertyjunction.co.za).

  * Company Name
  * Phone Number
  * Facsimile Number
  * Email Address
  * Website Address
  * City or Town & Country (Province)
  * Communications(Yes/No)

**7\. Resume** ****

We request the following information from a CareerSeeker in our resume form:

Personal Details, including:

  * Full Name
  * Date Of Birth 
  * ID Number (Optional)
  * Affirmative Action CareerSeeker (African/Coloured/Indian/Disabled/Female)
  * Phone Number
  * Additional Phone Number (optional)
  * Email Address
  * Location
  * Languages
  * Education Details
  * Employment History
  * Skills
  * Associations
  * Achievements
  * My Next Job
  * Availability
  * Searchability

This information is used for the Online Recruitment process and this includes sending CareerSeeker resumes to a Recruiter for the purpose of a CareerSeekers job application process where such resume data may then be stored by the Recruiter for future recruitment consideration. A Recruiter may also make contact with a CareerSeeker for recruitment opportunities as a result of a resume search conducted by the Recruiter on searchable resumes on the CareerJunction database. If we have trouble processing a request, the contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. CareerJunction does not store this information.

CareerSeekers who have been placed in a job through the CareerJunction Network are eligible for an online voucher that can be redeemed at [www.exclus1ves.co.za](http://www.exclus1ves.co.za/). The information we require for these purposes are employment details, recruiter details and personal details. The information will be stored for verification purposes only and will be treated as confidential. If a CareerSeeker gives us permission we may publish details of their placement.

**8\. Profile**

We request the following information from the user in our profile in order to search and enquire about any advertised autos or properties:  
Personal Details, including:

  * First Name and Last Name
  * Email Address

This information is used for the Online Enquiry process and this includes sending Seeker contact details to an Auto Dealer or Property Agent for the purpose of the Dealer of Agent to contact the Seeker regarding an enquiry that the Seeker have sent to the Dealer or Agent.

**9\. Cookies** ****

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie terminates.

We use a third-party tracking service Effective Measure that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate for usage and volume statistics to report on site traffic statistics. The Effective Measure Measurement Technology is used only for the collection of anonymous web site traffic statistics.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this site and Effective Measure only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**10\. Log Files** ****

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track users' movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**11\. Sharing** ****

We sometimes share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to personally identifiable information.

We also partner with third parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names or other information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. We will not voluntarily disclose any information about individual users to third parties, except as described in this privacy statement, or to comply with applicable laws or valid legal process, or to protect the rights or property of CareerJunction and its partner sites.

CareerJunction maintains relationships with outside service providers for some of the services offered through our site, for example MyGate and Virtual Card Services (VCS).

The information these providers make available may be presented in a "framed" format, where the CareerJunction border will surround the pages served by the service provider, or where pages have the look and feel of CareerJunction. In either case, the service provider is prominently identified. Please be aware that any information you provide on those framed pages is provided directly to those service providers and is subject to their security and privacy policies. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of these outside service providers because their privacy practices may differ from ours.

**12\. Links** ****

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that CareerJunction is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected on pages of this site.

**13\. Communications** ****

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify their username and password. Users also have the choice to subscribe to our newsletter. A user can unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time from both our site and the newsletter itself.

CareerJunction may use your information to contact you about promotions and services. You are entitled, at any stage, to opt out of this service, by clicking on the "opt out" option on the email correspondence. This will redirect you to the My Portfolio page where you will be able to unsubscribe from newsletters, promotional communications and/ or service announcements.

From time to time we may send out critical service announcements. Users are not able to unsubscribe from critical service announcements, which contain important information about the service.

**14\. Security and Data Storage** ****

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information online. When asked to enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number), the information is encrypted and is protected via secure sockets layer (SSL) encryption technology.

We also do everything in our power to protect user information offline. Access to all of our users' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our Client Service Manager) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure, access controlled environment. If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as their email address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal details provided to us. This can be done from the user's My Portfolio page or by emailing our Client Service Manager at [info@careerjunction.co.za](mailto:info@careerjunction.co.za).

**15\. Choice/Opt Out** ****

Users who no longer wish to allow their resume to be searchable by our subscribers may opt out of this facility by going to their My Portfolio page, to My Resume and select to be non-searchable. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter may opt out of receiving it by going to their My Portfolio page, to My Newsletter and select to not receive newsletters.

**16\. Blog Disclosure** ****

If you choose to submit information or comments to the blog on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

**17\. Notification of Changes** ****

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

**18\. Contact Us** ****

**Phone Us**  
+27 21 818 8600

**Fax us**  
+27 21 818 8609

**Email us**  

**Visit us**  
3 Fir Road  
Black River Park  
Third Floor  
Central Building  
Observatory  
7925  
South Africa (Western Cape)

**Snailmail Us**  
PO Box 87  
Century City  
7446

Effective Date: 1 September 2013
